roempire.com 2011-02-05

# :: RO Empire - Privacy Policy :: A Ragnarok Online Official Fansite ::

ROEmpire.com is committed to honoring the privacy of our members and visitors. This privacy policy covers personally identifiable information shared through the ROEmpire.com Service.

### What information does ROEmpire.com receive and how do we use it?

If you register as a ROEmpire.com Member or for various ROEmpire.com services, we ask you for your name, contact information, preferences, and certain demographic information. This information lets us provide personalized services and communicate separately with you. We also use aggregated information about the use of our services to evaluate our users' preferences, improve our programming, and facilitate third-party reporting of Internet usage.

Like most Web sites, we use small bits of data called "cookies" stored on users' computers to simulate a continuous connection. Cookies let us "remember" information about your preferences and allow you to move within our Service without reintroducing yourself. Most browsers let you easily see and control cookies. Some of our advertisers use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use general information about your visits to this and/or other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

### Can I choose what information I disclose?

While we need certain information to register you as a unique user and let you access personalized services, other requested information is optional and may be given at your discretion.

### What if I need to review or change the personal information I previously disclosed?

We encourage registered users to update and edit their personal information and keep it current. You can easily correct or update your personal information at any time after signing in.

### What kind of security is used to protect my information?

We store all user information in secure databases protected via a variety of access controls. This data is accessed only for the purposes specified in this privacy statement.

### Who has access to my information?

We do not share personally identifiable data with other companies unless you specifically tell us we can do so.
